Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Class Photographs
  - Graduation Photographs
    - 1960-1966
      - 1963, 8 x 10 neg., and 9 x 14 print (Box 15)
      - 1964, 8 x 10 and 8 x 10 print, Xerox of Print (Box 15)
      - 1965
        - Negative, 8 x 10 (Box 15)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
      - 1966, 8 x 10 neg., 8 x 10 print (Box 15)
    - 1967-1994
      - Negative, 1967; oversized (Map-case 230)
      - 1968
        - Print, 9 x 14 print (Box 15)
        - Negative, oversize (Map-case 230)
      - 1969
        - Print, Xerox of Print (Box 15)
        - Negative, oversize (Map-case 230)
      - 1970, 8 x 12neg. (Box 15)
      - 1971, oversized neg. (Map-case 230)
      - 1972, oversize neg. (Map-case 230)
      - 1973
        - Negative, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, 9x14 (Box 15)
      - 1974
        - Negative, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, Xerox of print (Box 15)
      - 1975, 8 x 12 neg. (Box 15)
      - 1976, oversized neg. (Map-case 230)
      - 1977, oversized neg. (Map-case 230)
      - 1978
        - Negative, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, 9 x 14 print (Box 15)
      - 1979
        - Negative, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, Xerox of print (Box 15)
      - 1980, 4 x 5, 8.5 x 12 negs. (Box 15)
      - 1981, 3 x 8 (Box 15)
        (consists of two 3 x 4 negatives)
      - 1982, oversized neg. (Map-case 230)
      - 1983 (Box 15)
      - 1984
        - Negative, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, Xerox of Print (Box 15)
      - 1987
        - Negative, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, 9 x 14 print (Box 15)
      - 1988
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Box 34)
        - Print, 9 x 14 (Box 15)
      - 1989
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, Xerox of Print (Box 15)
      - 1990
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Box 34)
      - 1991, oversized neg (Box 35)
      - 1992
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, Xerox of print (Box 15)
      - 1992 Black Medical Association/Latin American/Native American Medical Association Class of 1992, oversized print (Map-case 230)
      - 1993
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, 9x13 (Box 15)
      - 1994
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, Xerox of print (Box 15)
      - 1995
        - Negative, versized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
      - 1996
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
      - 1997
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Prrnt, oversized, stained (Map-case 230)
      - 1998
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
      - 1999
        - Negative, oversized (Box 35)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
      - 2002
        - Digital images on CD, (TIF), 6 x12 12 x 24 and 24 x 48, 300 dpi (Box 15)
        - Print, oversized (Map-case 230)
        - Print, 8.5 x 10.5 (Box 15)
      - 2003
        - Digital images on CD, (TIF), 6 x12 12 x 24 and 24 x 48, 300 dpi (Box 15)
      - 2004
        - Digital images on CD, (TIF), 6 x12 12 x 24 and 24 x 48, 300 dpi (Box 15)
        - Print, 8.5 x 10.5 (Box 15)
      - 2006, oversizedprint
- Buildings Photographs
  The Buildings Photographs series (1.25 linear feet) includes numerous black and white and color exterior and interior views of the buildings that make up the university medical complex. The series also features prints and negatives documenting the construction of various hospital structures. The most complete series of construction photographs exist for the Taubman Medical Library and the second Medical Science Building. This series also contains many images of older, medical buildings, since torn down. Photographs of the first two campus hospital structures, built in 1869 and 1875, were brought together into a separate grouping ("Nineteenth Century Buildings"), along with folders for other buildings from this period. This grouping also contains a file of miscellaneous copy negatives of drawings and photographs of the early campus. Further, the series includes numerous views of early buildings in the Catherine Street area, such as the Maternity Hospital, the Contagious Hospital and the Psychopathic Ward. The "Old Main" Hospital, built in 1925, has three folders within this series, one of which contains oversized pictures and another of which documents the demolition the building. The series is most thorough in documenting the medical building program from the late 1940s to the late 1960s. There are multiple external views and occasional construction photos of the first two Kresge buildings, the two Medical Science Buildings, the Children's Hospital and numerous others. The demolition of the "Old Main" Hospital and construction of the "new" University Hospital (Taubman Center) are well documented in the series. Significant for researchers documenting the development of university medical construction, there are several aerial views of the hospital complex (all prints, except for one color negative). One of these dates from 1964, and others were taken during the 1980s and 1990s.
  - Medical Campus Buildings
    - Aerial Views, Old Main Hospital, 1957; 1964-1969; undated; 4 folders; 2 oversize folders
      - Aerial viess, undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
      - Aerial views, 1957; 1964-1969; negatives (Box 15)
      - Outsize aerial prints (Map-case 230)
      - Outsize aerial color transparency (Map-case 230)
    - Aerial Views, University Hospital and Medical Center
      - 1986, 1991; 1993 (Box 15)
      - 1997, 1999 (Box 15)
      - Undated (Box 15)
      - Outsize aerial prints, Undated (Map-case 230)
    - Beal Residence (formerly Psychopathic Ward), 1964; undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Buhl Building, 1963-1964; 1990; undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Catherine Street Hospital Buildings, undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Children's Hospital, 1957-1958; 1961; 1967; undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
      (see also the Dedications sub-series in the Photographs (Topical) Series)
    - Contagious Hospital, 1956; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Dentistry Building, undated; print and negative (Box 15)
    - Dietetics House, 1961; undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Furstenberg Center, undated; negatives (Box 15)
    - "Old" Interns' Quarters, 1959; negatives (Box 15)
    - Kellogg Eye Center, 1985; 1991; undated; negatives (Box 15)
    - Kresge Hearing Research Institute, 1958; 1964; 1996; undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Kresge Building I, 1952-1958; undated; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - Kresge Building II, 1961-1964; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - "Old Main" Hospital, 1924; 1926; 1960; undated; 2 folders; 1 oversize folders in drawer 230; prints and negatives (Box 15)
    - "Old Main" Hospital demolition, 1989; print, negatives and slide (Box 15)
    - Maternal and Child Health Center, 1989; 1990; undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - "Old" Maternity Hospital, 1946; 1950; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Medical Center, 1955-1957; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Medical Center/University Hospital (Box 16)
    - Medical Science Building I, 1956-1965; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Medical Science Building II, 1964-1967; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Medical Science Building III, 1988; 1989; undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - Mental Health Research Institute, 1959; 1967; negatives (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous and Unidentified, undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - Mott Children's Hospital, 1987; 1990; undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute, 1938; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Nineteenth Century Buildings
      - Anatomical Laboratory, undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
      - Early Campus Views, 1854-1885; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
      - Homeopathic College and Hospital, 1914; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
      - Medical School, undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
      - University Hospital (a.k.a. Pavilion Hospital), undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - North Ingalls Building (St. Joseph Hospital), 1958; 1990; undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - Nurses' Residence (Pemberton-Welsch), undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Outpatient Building, 1950-1967; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Outpatient Building (North), undated; prints and transparency (Box 16)
    - Passageways, 1958; 1967; undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - Pathology Building, 1964; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Pharmacology Building, undated; print and negative (Box 16)
    - Psychopathic Ward, see Beal Residence (Box 16)
    - School of Nursing, 1958; 1967; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Public Health Building, undated; negative and print (Box 16)
    - Rackham Graduate School Architectural Details, undated (Box 16)
    - Radiation Therapy Unit, 1954; negatives (Box 16)
    - Ronald McDonald House, 1987; negatives (Box 16)
    - Satellite Facilities, undated; negatives (Box 16)
    - Simpson Building, 1967; 1989; undated; prints, negatives and slide (Box 16)
    - Surgical Ward (part of Catherine Street Hospital Complex), undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Taubman Library, 1979-1980; 7 folders prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Towsley Center, 4 folders (Box 16)
      (also see Towsley Center under Topical Medical Related Photographs
    - Unidentified Medical Buildings, undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - University Hospital, 1987; 1991; 1994; undated; 2 folders prints, negatives, and transparencies (Box 16)
    - Veterans' Administration Hospital, undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Veterans' Readjustment Center, 1946-1981; prints and negatives (Box 16)
    - Women's Hospital, 1947; 1958; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
  - Other Buildings and General Views
    - Campus Views, Miscellaneous, undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
      (one oversized photograph of a lithograph located separately in drawer 230)
    - Ann Arbor Views, 1991; 1992; undated; prints and negatives (Box 16)
- Topical Files
  The Topical Photographs series (13.5 linear feet) contains two sub-series: Medical Related photographs and Non-Medical Related Photographs. The first subseries includes prints and negatives from a variety of medical related contexts including class reunions, lectures, graduation, medical procedures, and other activities and events. The second subseries includes prints and negatives from a variety of non-medical related contexts outside the University of Michigan Healthcare system, evidence of the broadening role of BMC Media Services on campus. These prints and negatives document academic and administrative units within the University of Michigan. They include award ceremonies, class reunions, building dedications, graduations and other events and activities. Within the Topical Photographs series, academic, administrative, and medical groups and units arranged alphabetically. Within each department or unit, folders are listed alphabetically. The Topical Photographs series contains numerous photographs produced by BMC and used in various brochures, bulletins, and other publications. Of special interest are three folders that document the clinical training of students. Based on dress and other evidence, these photographs are probably from around the end of the nineteenth century. One folder of "ward photographs" taken in the old Catherine Street Hospital buildings probably dates from the same time period. In both cases, the presence of photos from the Gibson photographic studio helps to date the files. Also of note are photos from certain "historic events," such as a visit from Dr. Christian Bernard, and pictures of early heart and lung transplant operations (1968 and 1969).
  - Medical Related Topical Files
    - Adolescent Clinic Program, 1983; 1989; negatives, contact sheets, prints and consent forms (Box 17)
    - Allergy
      - John M. Sheldon Society, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Alumni and Development, 2000-2001
      - Abrams [Gerald D.], 2001 (Box 17)
      - Art and Decoration
        - Artwork, Photo, and Bio, 2000 (Box 17)
        - Oil Painting William Kelley and Cornerstone Sign (Dana Hall), 2000 (Box 17)
        - Painting and Mural Section, 2000 (Box 17)
        - Painting in Kresge Lobby, 2000 (Box 17)
        - Towsley Hall Placques, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Dr. [Alfred E.] Chang with Family and Dean, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Dr. Coran with Jesus Andrade, 2001 (Box 17)
      - Dr. George Demuth, Dr. Keonig Talking, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Graduation
        - Graduation, 2000 (Box 17)
        - Medical School Honors Convocation, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Heritage Program, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Hiss and Van Harrison, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Inauguration of Professorship, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Luncheon/Sesquicentennial [150th anniversary] Address/Marshall Nirnberg, 2000 (Box 17)
      - M-4 Class Picnic, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Match Day, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Medical Education Day, 2001 (Box 17)
      - Pharmacology Equipment, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Pharmacology Jars, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Professionalism as a Casualty, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Ronald Koening, Penny Morris, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Senior Class Luncheon, 20001 (Box 17)
      - Time Line, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Alumni Reunions, negatives
      - Class of 1907, 1932 (Box 17)
      - Class of 1910, undated (Box 17)
      - Class of 1917, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Class of 1920, 1950; 1956 (Box 17)
      - Class of 1926, 1966 (Box 17)
      - Class of 1929, 1964 (Box 17)
      - Class of 1931m, 1966 (Box 17)
      - Class of 1951, 1966 (Box 17)
      - Classes of 1916, 1922, 1927, 1932, 1937, 1941, 1942, 1952, 1962, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - Hodge Society, 1966 (Box 17)
    - American Lung Association, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Anatomy Training (Students), undated (Box 17)
    - Anesthesiology
      - Brochure
        - 1992 (Box 17)
        - Undated (Box 17)
      - Burned Trach Tube, 1997 (Box 17)
      - Cadaver, 1997 (Box 17)
      - C-Arm Positions, 1998 (Box 17)
      - Cart Set-Up, 1999 (Box 17)
      - Chair Controls, 1993 (Box 17)
      - Difficult Airway Procedure, 1999 (Box 17)
      - Dissections, 1997 (Box 17)
      - Graduation, 2001 (Box 17)
      - Group Shot for Poster Presentation, 19991 (Box 17)
      - Instruments
        - 1995 (Box 17)
        - 1996 (Box 17)
      - Kole/Rosenberg, 1996 (Box 17)
      - Monitor, 1996 (Box 17)
      - Mott O.R. [Operating Room] Procedures, 1992 (Box 17)
      - Procedure Photos, 1997 (Box 17)
      - Pt. Equipment (Pain Clinic), 1993 (Box 17)
    - Biochemistry
      - Awards
        - 2 Students Award Ceremony, undated (Box 17)
        - Ceremony, 1993 (Box 17)
        - Christianson Award, 1995 (Box 17)
        - Graduate Student Awards/Christiansen Award, 1993 (Box 17)
        - Jay Dewiewiakoski Award
          - 1991 (Box 17)
          - 1994 (Box 17)
      - Biochemistry Seminar, Poster session, Awards Reception, 1996 (Box 17)
      - Brochure, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Dave Turner and Anne Vojtek for Brochure Update, 1996 (Box 17)
      - DNA Model (Studio), 1992 (Box 17)
      - Grad School Application Seminar, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Group Shots of Class of '94, 1994 (Box 17)
      - Malvor N. Christensen Fellowship Presentation, 1992 (Box 17)
      - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 17)
      - Seminar, Poster Session, Awards Reception, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Staff in Lab, 1993 (Box 17)
      - Students Prep for Poster Session, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Walther Review, 1992 (Box 17)
      - Walther, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Biomedical Communications (BMC)
      - Brochure, 1986[?] (Box 17)
      - 1993, undated; negatives and slides (Box 17)
        (work samples, storefront)
    - Biomedical Engineering
      - Bio Eng at Work, 1997 (Box 17)
      - Burned Data Shield, 1993 (Box 17)
      - Equipment, 1996 (Box 17)
      - Goldstein, 1990 (Box 17)
      - Photography for Display, 1991 (Box 17)
      - Quality Team, 1993 (Box 17)
      - Syringe with Broken Glass Inside, 1992 (Box 17)
      - Total Quality Conference, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Biomedical Sciences
      - Brochure, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Cardiology
      - Brochures
        - 1992 (Box 17)
        - (Residents Training), 1996 (Box 17)
      - Cardiology Catheter Lab, 1990 (Box 17)
      - Heart Catheter Studio Shoot, 1992 (Box 17)
      - Heart Newsletter, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Lab Group, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Cardiovascular Research, 1998
      - Group with Betsy Nabel, 1998 (Box 17)
      - Group, 1998 (Box 17)
    - Cellular and Molecular Biology
      - Brochure
        - 1991 (Box 17)
        - (Second Shoot), 1991 (Box 17)
        - 1996 (Box 17)
      - Heart Newsletter Contacts, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Presentation, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Child and Adolescent Psychology
      - CAPH, 1990 (Box 17)
      - Cheryl King and Judy (?), 1995 (Box 17)
    - Class Reunion 1938 and Faculty Meetings, 1940s-1950s, undated prints (Box 18)
    - Clinical Research Center, 1995 (Box 18)
    - Clinical Training (Students), undated (Box 18)
    - Communicative Disorders Clinic
      - Brochure, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Complex Systems, 1996; 2001 (Box 18)
    - Construction Management
      - Cancer Center Facade, 1997 (Box 18)
      - Dead Pine Trees, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Continuing Medical Education (CME)
      - Business Office, 1987 (Box 18)
      - Continuing Education, 1987 (Box 18)
      - Educational Resources, 1987 (Box 18)
      - Extramural Education., 1987 (Box 18)
      - Internal Medicine Administration, 1987 (Box 18)
      - LRC, 1987; 2 envelopes (Box 18)
      - Post Graduation, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Cystic Fibrosis, 1993
      - Student Testing, 1991 (Box 18)
    - Dean's Office
      - Dean Bole Portrait Unveiling, 1997 (Box 18)
      - Dean's Office, undated; prints and negatives (Box 18)
      - Golightly Education Center Shoot, 1994 (Box 18)
      - Medical Student Orientation, 1992 (Box 18)
      - Scholarship Dinner, 2001 (Box 18)
      - The Double Edge Helix, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Dedications, prints and negatives
      - C. S. Mott Children's Hospital and others, 1960-1967; undated (Box 18)
      - Crosby negative, 1982 (Box 18)
      - Library, 1971; negatives (Box 18)
      - Towsley Center, 1969; prints and negatives (Box 18)
      - University Hospital, 1986; negatives (Box 18)
    - Dermatology
      - Group Shot, 1995 (Box 18)
      - Lloyd Carr Lecture, 1999 (Box 18)
      - Taylor Professorship, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Diabetes, 1996 (Box 18)
    - Dietetics
      - Brochure
        - 1990, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Cakes and Halloween Cake, 1995 (Box 18)
      - Complete Qualitative Nutrition Group Shot, 1992 (Box 18)
      - Food and Nutrition Group, 1992 (Box 18)
      - Graduation
        - Dietetic Interns
          - 1994 (Box 18)
          - 1999 (Box 18)
          - 2000 (Box 18)
          - 2001 (Box 18)
        - Food and Nutrition
          - 1995 (Box 18)
          - 1996 (Box 18)
          - 1997 (Box 18)
          - 1998 (Box 18)
      - Home Page Project, 1995 (Box 18)
      - Person and Computer, 1989 (Box 18)
      - Photos for Training, 1992 (Box 18)
      - Mom, Baby, Diet, 1993 (Box 18)
      - Mothers Day Cake, 1996 (Box 18)
      - Swain Retirement, 1992 (Box 18)
      - X-mas [Christmas] Cakes, 1995 (Box 18)
    - Diversity Calendar
      - 1993, 1994; 2 folders prints and negatives (Box 18)
      - 1994
        - Cover Photos (Box 18)
        - Portraits Not Used in Calendar
          - Carter, Carolanne (Box 18)
          - Hewlett, Koki(?) (Box 18)
          - Kwong, Lik (Box 18)
          - Lee, Jeanna (Box 18)
          - Little, Robert (Box 18)
          - Meldrum, Craig (Box 18)
          - Richardson, Wayne (Box 18)
          - Wakefield, Thomas (Box 18)
          - Unidentified (Box 18)
        - Portraits Used in Calendar
          - Ashlock, Glen (Box 18)
          - Azizi, Jahan (Box 18)
          - Dela Fuente, Tessie (Box 18)
          - Hunte, Althea (Box 18)
          - Jamerson, Dr. (Box 18)
          - Martinez, Cathy (Box 18)
          - Neel, James (Box 18)
          - O'Jibway, Christine (Box 18)
          - Quint, Leslie (Box 18)
          - Smith, Caesanea (Box 18)
          - Spangler, Bill (Box 18)
          - Thompson, John and Ben (Box 18)
    - Emergency Medicine
      - Candids, 1993 (Box 18)
      - Grad Class Photo, undated (Box 18)
      - Grad Party Group, 1995 (Box 18)
      - Residents Dinner, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Endocrinology and Metabolism
      - JDS Foundation Center Event, 2000 (Box 18)
      - Schembechler Memorial Conference, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Events
      - BMC Educom, 1989; negatives (Box 18)
      - Christian Barnard, lecture and press conference, undated; prints and negatives (Box 18)
      - Employee Appreciation Week, undated; prints and negatives (Box 18)
      - Ground Breaking, 1981; negatives (Box 18)
      - Heart Transplants #1 and #2 (Philip Barnum), 1968; undated; negatives (Box 18)
      - Ice Sculpture or, 1988; 1989; negatives (Box 18)
      - Lung Transplant, 1969; negatives (Box 18)
      - MHRI, 1990; 1991; negatives (Box 18)
      - Move to new hospital, Mott/Child Maternal Health, 1990; negatives (Box 18)
      - Move to new hospital, Psych, 1990; negatives (Box 18)
      - Receptions, 1969-1971; negatives (Box 18)
      - Towsley Center, 1987; negatives (Box 18)
      - Tree Planting Ceremony, New Gen. Care Site, 1995; negatives (Box 18)
      - Unidentified event, undated; outsize print (Map-case 230)
      - White Coat ceremony, undated; contact sheets (Box 18)
    - Executive Director's Office
      - Dr. Watt's Reception, 2001 (Box 18)
      - Zuidema Retirement Party, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Facilities (Box 19)
      - Bio Hazard Buckets, 1994; 1 folders; 1 envelopes (Box 19)
      - Boxes of Recyclables, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Cardboard Cont., 1993 (Box 19)
      - Chemo Waste Bucket, 1994 (Box 19)
      - CMA Photos, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Containers, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Disposal Booklets, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Facilities
        - 1993, 1 folders (Box 19)
        - 1994, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Hazardous Waste, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Labels for Waste Poster, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Material Management, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Poster Shots, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Recycle Containers for Poster, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Recycle Logo, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Recycling, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Sharps, 1994; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Waste Management, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Family Medicine
      - Dr. Ryan with Patient, 1999 (Box 19)
      - East Ann Arbor [Health Center] Family Medicine Apps (individual portraits), 2000 (Box 19)
      - East Ann Arbor, Ypsi, Briarwood, Chelsea and Dexter Buildings, 1997 (Box 19)
      - Family Practice Interns, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Multiethnic Brochure, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Food and Nutrition see Dietetics (Box 19)
    - Friends of UM, 1989; 1991 (Box 19)
    - Furstenberg Center, 1974; 1978; 1989; undated (Box 19)
    - Gastroenterology, 1996 (Box 19)
    - General Medicine, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Genetics
      - Dr. Innez, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Genetic Counseling Program Summer Science Program Week 1, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Geriatrics
      - Awards Luncheon, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Devito Award, 2001 (Box 19)
      - Florence Tillman, 1997 (Box 19)
      - Geriatrics, various dates (Box 19)
      - Mobility Lab, 2001 (Box 19)
      - New Hope Clinic
        - 2001 (Box 19)
        - (Grand Opening), 2001 (Box 19)
      - Turner Arthritis Program, 1996 (Box 19)